airjamaica.com 2010-12-09

# Air Jamaica

_Last Modified: August 2006_

**Protecting the privacy of our customers**  
Air Jamaica Limited respects the privacy of its customers. Your personal information is collected online to provide you with the most personalized service possible. The information is used to contact customers when necessary and as protection from fraud and illegal activity. This document outlines the type of information collected, how it is used, as well as your role in protecting and correcting personal information provided to Air Jamaica via this website. Air Jamaica reserves the right to amend or update this policy at any time in its sole discretion without notice to users. All updated policies will be published. We encourage you to review our Privacy and Security policies whenever you visit our website so you will always understand how your information will be used. 

**What personal information is collected by Air Jamaica**  
Air Jamaica collects data on user and site activity, including pages accessed, domains, browsers and locations. Return e-mail addresses from users who send e-mail to any of the e-mail addresses listed on our site are also stored. On-line members can choose to provide destination preferences as well as other personal information that will be used primarily to provide quick service without having to re-enter information.     
In order to register on our booking site and complete a booking, users must provide the following information:   
**_Traveler Information_**  
• Prefix  
• First Name  
• Last Name  (mandatory)  
• Frequent Flyer Number  
• Seat Preference  
• Special Requests  
 ** _Contact Numbers/ Email_**  
• Business  
• Home  (mandatory)  
• Cell  
• Fax  
• Email 1  (mandatory)  
 ** _Payment Information_**  
• Credit Card Type  (mandatory)  
• Card Number (mandatory)  
• Card Holder (mandatory)  
• Expiration Date (mandatory)  
 ** _Billing Address_**  
• Street Address  
• City  
• State/Province  
• Zip/Postal Code  
• Country  
For details on the Privacy Policy of the Booking Engine please visit the Privacy Policy link found on our booking page or contact [privacy@sabre.com](mailto:privacy@sabre.com).

In order to enroll online in our 7th Heaven frequent flyer program and sign up for special offers, users must provide the following information: 

**7th Heaven** **  
**•  Title (mandatory)  
• First Name (mandatory)  
• Last Name (mandatory)  
• Mailing Address (mandatory)  
• City (mandatory)  
• State (mandatory)  
• Country (mandatory)  
• Zip / Postal Code  
• Home Telephone (mandatory)  
• Business Telephone  
• Mobile Telephone  
• Email Address (mandatory)  
• Occupation   
• Other Frequent Flyer Membership  
• Security Question & Answer (mandatory)

 **Air Jamaica 7th Heaven Rewards World Mastercard** **  
**Please visit<https://www.juniper.com/app/ccsite/legal/overviewDynamic.jsp>

 **Special Offers**  
• Last Name  (mandatory)  
• First Name  (mandatory)  
• Email Address  (mandatory)  
• Mobile  
• Frequent Flyer Number

In order to register for Cargo Bookings originating out of Kingston, Montego Bay, Miami or New York users must provide the following information:

**Air Jamaica Cargo**

**_Shipment Details_**  
• Total Pieces (mandatory)  
• Total Weight (mandatory)  
• Description of Goods (mandatory)  
• Air waybill Number  
 ** _Dimensions (cm)_**  
• Length   
• Width  
• Height  
• Pieces  
 ** _Contact Details_**  
• Booking made by (mandatory)  
• Contact Number (mandatory)  
• Email Address (mandatory)  
 ** _Flight Delivery Details_**  
• Origin (mandatory)  
• Destination (mandatory)  
• Drop-off Date (mandatory)  
• Drop-off Time  
• Flight Number  
• Flight Date  
 ** _Shipper/Consignee Information_**  
• Shipper Name  
• Consignee Name  
• Broker

**How Air Jamaica uses this information**  
Your username and password are used for personal identification. E-mail addresses provided for booking are used to contact customers for customer service, if necessary, and also to send booking confirmations. E-mail addresses provided by frequent flyers are used to send account information and possibly notification of special offers. Users may unsubscribe from this mailing list at any time.  Users registered to receive special promotion notifications will have such information sent to the specified e-mail address. Return e-mail addresses are used solely to respond to e-mails received and not for any other purpose. The personal information provided in the booking area is used for registration and reservation purposes.   
From time to time, we may use the profile information provided for marketing purposes. Air Jamaica will not disclose your personal information provided to us on-line outside the boundaries outlined in this privacy notice without prior permission. 

**Who has access to your personal information** **  
**Only you and Air

Jamaica staff who have a “genuine business interest” can see any personal information you submit on this web site.     
By "genuine business interest," we mean:     
• Customer service. For example, if you send a request through our website, support representatives need to see that request in order to cater to your needs.   
• Maintaining the site. Sometimes our technical staff may view data in the course of their work.  
• Research and marketing. In order to keep improving our services, we compile data from users of this site. 

Air 

Jamaica reserves the right to share certain personal information with its partners or affiliates (e.g. hotels, car rental companies and promotional groups) on terms that Air Jamaica believes reasonable to safeguard the integrity and privacy of your information. Such affiliates may use the information for research or marketing purposes. Air Jamaica shall not be liable for misuse of information in respect of such access. 

**Accessing your personal information** **  
**On-line members may access and update their personal information provided to our booking site by signing into their user profile accounts using their username and password. All other personal information must be updated by contacting an Air Jamaica office.   

 **Other points to note about your privacy** **  
**You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and private account information. Be extremely careful with such information especially when on-line. Air Jamaica may disclose member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of Air Jamaica Limited or when we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify or bring legal action against a person who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. Our website also includes links to other websites. Please note the privacy and security policies of these websites. Air

Jamaica is not responsible for the use of any information that you may submit to these websites. It is also recommended that you pay attention to the disclaimers on all sites to which you may choose to subscribe.
